Guide to the Samuel Ruben Papers RG.015
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series II: Exhibition, 1975-1979; 6294; A zinc mercuric dioxysulfate/zinc Sulfate cell, a non alkaline dry cell, was pasted onto number 40 of an inventory list (box 2, folder 3).
  - Subseries C: Photographs, circa 1970-1979; 6299
    - Photograph Numbers 11 - 22, 1979?; 6313 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Photograph Numbers 23 - 41, 1979?; 6314 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Smithsonian Institution Photographs, 1970; 6315 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated; 6319 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Subseries D: Realia, 6306
    - Plaque, 1979; 6303 (Box 4, Object 4)
    - Battery, undated; 6304 (Box 4, Object 5)
    - Keys, undated; 6317 (Box 4, Object 6)
- Series III: The Ruben Scholarships, 1967-1968; 6400
  - The Ruben Scholarships, 1967; 6401 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Series IV: Articles, 1967-1968; 6402 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Articles, 1967-1968; 6403 (Box 3, Folder 12)